like4like.org 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Like4Like.org

We respect the privacy of our visitors and are obliged to protect your online safety by keeping your privacy anytime you visit our site.

Our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use suggest you clear explanation referring to your personal data provided to us or any data we may collect from you.

This Privacy Policy is updated periodically; so you should review it from time to time.

## Gathered Information

During the operations of our website a data information can be collected and handled by means of the following actions:

  * Data regarding your visit(s) to our website and any resources used are collected. The following is included and not limited to location data, weblogs, traffic data, and any other communication information.
  * Any forms you filled out on our site let us gather data such as registering for information or when you complete a purchase.
  * If for any reason you contact our administration, support or site we may collect information.

### We will never collect or store CC/DC data.

## Use of cookies

There can be cases when we may use cookies to collect information regarding our services in a mathematical collection for our website and our advertisers. No personal details will be shared that could identify you. Any information collected is statistical data about our visitors and how they have used our site. We may collect information about your common internet use with a cookie file. The cookies are automatically downloaded to your computer and are kept on the hard drive. The required data by the cookie helps us improve our website and services suggested to you. You have the opportunity to decline cookies by setting your browser options to decline all cookies. But remember: if you decline the download of cookies some features of our site may not work.

## The Use of Your Information

We implemented [GDPR Privacy Policy](https://www.like4like.org/gdpr-implementation.php "GDPR Privacy Policy Implementation") and it is the binding part of this Policy.

Information assembled referring to you helps us improve and offer services you need. You can see how we may use your data in the list below:

  * Any request you make of our site let us use the information you provided us with, relating to the products or services we have. If we have your permission we may also send information on products or services you may be interested in.
  * Changes or Improvements made to the site can guarantee use of your information, with regard to notification of such changes.

We may use data or let third parties use information that is not related to goods or services you may be interested in. This can be done only in the case of your permission.

If you don't want to give consent for our site or third party you can use the opportunity to decline. If you decline once we will remove your details from any third party communications or mailings.

### The Information we have about you will be stored on secure servers. Transaction data is encrypted for your safety.

Note: data via online transmission is not entirely secure. We cannot warrant total protection and security data, we only take all reasonable action to protect information sent to us electronically. Transmission of any data by you is at your own risk. The responsibility for the passwords safety and confidentiality is your own.

If you violate our Privacy policy, Terms and conditions, or any other regulations that we have on our community website, for any reason, we hold the right to ban your account, and store hashed values of your email and IP address to protect us from any further violations that you may inflict on our system and community members.

## Information Exposer

At times we may reveal personal information to persons in our group. This can include subsidiaries, holding companies or any other if applicable.

Third Party disclosure may happen for the following reasons:

  * In the case of selling any or all of our business to a third party, your information may be shared.
  * When we are legally required to, we may disclose information about you and your visits to our sites.
  * In order to prevent fraud, we may also disclose information.

## Third Party Links

Third party links may be found on our site. These third party links have their own privacy policy. By clicking on the link you agree to their privacy policy to which we have no control of and we are not responsible for third party links.

## Cancellation And Refund Policy

### Cancellation Policy

Like4Like.org believes in helping its customers as far as possible and has, therefore, a liberal cancellation policy. Under this policy:

  * Cancellations will be considered only if the request is made within 24 hours of placing an order. However, the cancellation request will not be entertained if the orders have been communicated to the vendors/merchants and they have initiated the process of shipping them.
  * There is no cancellation of orders placed under the Same Day Delivery category.
  * Like4Like.org does not accept cancellation requests for items (points, credits, tokens) that you are already used.
  * In case you feel that the product received is not as shown on the site or as per your expectations, you must bring it to the notice of our customer service within 24 hours of receiving the product. The Customer Service Team after looking into your complaint will take an appropriate decision.

### Refund Policy

When you buy our products/services, your purchase is covered by our 1-day money-back guarantee. If you are, for any reason, not entirely happy with your purchase and/or haven't used all purchased points (credits, tokens), we will cheerfully issue a full refund. To request a refund, simply contact us with your purchase details within one (1) day of your purchase. Please include your order number (sent to you via email after ordering) and optionally tell us why you’re requesting a refund – we take customer feedback very seriously and use it to constantly improve our products and quality of service. Refunds are not being provided for services that you already have used because our network fills your account balance (adding points/credits/tokens) immediately after purchase is done. Refunds are being processed within 7 days period.

## Contact Information

For questions, further information, requests or comments please feel free to contact us via support center.

#### Date of Last Revision: November 26, 2019

Like4Like.org

Social Media Exchange

is a network that will help you grow your social presence for FREE.

\- We allow you to look and choose who you want to like, subscribe, follow, view, circle, hit, share and skip those who you are not interested in.  
\- We do not sell likes, subscribes, friends, followers, views, hits, circles and shares.  
\- We abide by Twitters Rules, Facebooks Policies, Google Conditions, etc...  
\- We will never request for usernames or passwords of your social network accounts and will never post, tweet or update status from your accounts.  
\- We have a strict NO Bot, NO Macro, and NO Automation policy.
